{
    "id": "75ac2533900c455780a86ef57aec9d89",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His grandfather is …………………………..",
            "description": "Dead is an adjective. Died is a verb. Adjectives can be used as subject complements. ",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "dead"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His grandparents have ………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "dead"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………………. in",
            "description": "The present perfect is not used with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "has graduated",
                "graduated",
                "had graduated"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………………. me of her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reminds",
                "remembers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… me a visit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "gave",
                "paid"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He objected …………………………… sitting there.",
            "description": "A pronoun used to modify a gerund is usually in its possessive form.",
            "answers": [
                "to me",
                "to my",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are looking forward to …………………………….. you soon.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after look forward to.",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………………………. boy he is!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a foolish",
                "foolish a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Tell me where ………………………………..",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the subject goes before the auxiliary verb.",
            "answers": [
                "are you going",
                "you are going"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ………………………………… another application.",
            "description": "Had better is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "send",
                "to send",
                "sent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you went there, you ………………………………… see him.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ............................... this, I would be wrong.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}